The humanoids must first be destroyed.
必须首先消灭这些人类
You will re-enter cells
to conserve energy.
为了节省能力， 你们得重新进入格子间
Keep back!
后退！
Your gun.
你的枪
You've killed him, you murderer.
你杀了他，你这个杀人犯
- No. He is fortunate. I spared him.
- You mean you missed him.
- 不。他很幸运。我饶了他  - 你是说你没打中吧
Silence! I could have destroyed him
if I wanted to.
闭嘴！我本可以杀了他的，如果我想的话
- Shall I kill them now?
- No, that will not be necessary.
- 我现在该杀了他们吗？  - 不, 并没有必要
I'm sure the Cybermen
will have a use for them.
我能肯定，赛博人能好好利用他们
You will make excellent
experimental specimens.
你们将成为绝佳的实验样品
Oh, let me help him, please!
噢, 让我帮他一下, 拜托！
No tricks.
别耍花招
Still think you can bargain with the Cybermen?
还觉得你可以跟赛博人谈条件？
Certainly. This time on our terms.
当然, 这次得按我们的条件来
I wish to speak to the Controller.
我要同管理员谈话
I wish to speak to the Controller!
He is now prepared.
现在他已经准备好了
Release him.
放把出去吧
They're coming.
他们来了
Now, gentlemen, you will see how
I shall use the power of the Cybermen.
现在, 先生们, 你们将会见识到我是如何利用赛博人的力量的
Use, maybe, but you'll never
control the Cybermen.
利用, 有可能; 但你永远别想控制住赛博人
- Behind you.  - Stop!
- 在你后面  - 停下！
You know what this can do to you.
你知道这个会把你怎么样
Toberman, it is good that you are back.
Toberman, 你回来真是太好了
Watch them.
看着他们
- Doctor, he seems er...
- Yes, Jamie, yes.
- 博士, 他似乎...  - 是的, Jamie, 是的
I shall let you be revitalised, to survive.
我该让你充电了, 否则活不下去了
It must be now.
现在就得
Come forward. Slowly.
往前面来, 慢慢地
- Be careful.  - Leave this to me.
- 小心点  - 把这交给我吧
You are absolutely crazy to trust them!
你觉得是疯了, 居然相信他们！
You think so?
你这么觉得？
Then perhaps you and your colleagues
had better join him. Go on. Go on!
也许你和你的同事们最好跟他去, 走, 走！
- The girl stays with us.  - No!
- 这女孩留在我们这里  - 不！
She is our hostage.
他是我们的人质
Close the hatch.
关上舱门
You seem to be in trouble.
你看来有麻烦了
The energy...
能量
levels...are...low.
水平...低
We...will...survive.
我们...得...活下去
You will help us.
你得帮助我们
You will...help...us...
你得...帮助...我们
Yes. Yes, certainly.
是的, 是的, 当然了
- Jamie, Professor.
- You don't mean to say you're going to help them?
- Jamie, 教授  - 你不是想说你打算帮助他们吧？
Surely not. You can't support these creatures!
当然不能. 你不能帮这些怪物啊！
I think it best. Come on.
我已经想好了, 来吧
Come along.
过来
That's it.
就这样
Do...you...understand...the...machine?
你...能...搞懂...那个...机器吗？
Yes. One moment.
是的, 等一下
Have you taken leave of your senses?
Let's help Victoria.
你丧失判断力了吗？我们来帮 Victoria
In a moment, Jamie.
等一下, Jamie
(DOCTOR) Now, are you ready?
现在， 你准备好了吗？
We will survive.
我们会活下去
We will sur...
我们会活...
Now, where would you rather
have him - in or out of there?
现在, 你是愿意他待在里面呢, 还是外面？
Oh, I see what you mean.
哦, 我明白你的意思了
Only we must make sure
that he stays in there.
只是我们必须得确保他会待在里面
Do you really believe you can bargain
with those terrible Cybermen?
你真的相信你可以同那些可怕的赛博人讲条件？
That is our concern, not yours.
这是我们的事情, 不关你事
I'm talking to him, not you.
我在跟他说话, 不是你
They will have to agree to our plan.
他们将不得不同意我们的计划
Told you we shouldn't have touched it.
跟你说过我们本不该动它的
Yes. Turn it off. It's out of control.
是的。关掉它, 失控了
(NOISE DIES DOWN)
It's taken over.
被他们接管了？
I think not.
我觉得没有
There must be some sort
of internal timing mechanism.
肯定有某种内部计时机制
Jamie, I hope you made
those ropes secure.
Jamie，我期望你把绳子绑牢了
The King of Beasties himself
couldnae get out of that?
那个怪兽之王不能自己跑出来吧？
Jamie, remind me to give you
a lesson in tying knots some time.
Jamie, 回头提醒我找个时间教你如何打结
What do you hope to gain from this?
你想通过这个达到什么目的？
- That does not concern you.
- They might as well know.
- 那不关你事  - 他们可能也知道
We are going to build a better world.
我们要建造一个更好的世界
(CALLUM) Better? But who for?
更好？对谁更好？
I told you to watch the door.
我让你看好门的
Aagh!
啊！
Toberman.
Toberman.﻿
Victoria.
Victoria.﻿
- You have done well.  - Toberman!
- 你做得很好  - Toberman!
Silence.
安静
He is now under our control.
他现在处于我们控制之下了
Open the tombs.
打开墓室
No.
不
You have broken your promise.
你已经打破你的诺言了
Cybermen do not promise.
赛博人不做承诺
Such ideas have no value.
这样的观念没有价值
Open.
打开
No.
不
That gun will not harm me.
那把枪伤害不了我
Aagh!
啊！
Look what they've done.
看看他们干了啥
You are not like them. You're a man
like us. You must help us.
你跟他们不一样, 你是我们的一员, 你必须帮助我们
He has killed Kaftan.
You must help us.
他已经杀了 Kaftan, 你必须帮助我们
You will report to the surface.
你得向地面报告情况
(UNINTELLIGIBLE NOISES)
Jamie, the hatch!
Jamie, 舱门！
The gun, Jamie!
枪, Jamie!
There's another one, Doctor!
这里还有一个，博士！
(CRASHING)
Are there any more?
还有吗？
No. It's gone quiet.
I'll close the hatch.
没了, 安静下来了。我去关上舱门
Wait a minute.
We'd better go down there.
等一下, 我们最好下去
- Oh, no, not again!
- It's the only way to make sure.
- 噢不，别再下去了！  - 只有这样才能确认
- I'll go with you.
- No. You stay and look after Victoria.
- 我跟你一起去  - 不, 你留在这里照看 Victoria
I'll take somebody else.
我另外带个人去
Toberman.
Toberman﻿
You see what these creatures
have done to you?
你看到这些怪物对你做了什么吧？
They've tried to make you like them.
Do you understand?
他们想把你变得跟他们一样, 你明白吗？
They've tried to make you their slave.
They just want to use you.
他们试图把你变成他们的奴隶．他们想利用你
They are evil. Think of Kaftan.
他们是邪恶的, 想想 Kaftan
- Evil!
- They must be destroyed, you see?
- 邪恶！  - 必须摧毁他们, 你明白吗？
Evil must be destroyed.
邪恶必须被摧毁
Now, come.
现在, 来吧
Destroyed!
摧毁！
Come on.
快来
Come on!
快来！
- Good luck.  - Thank you.
- 祝你好运  - 谢谢你
- Doctor, the gun.
- I shan't need that.
- 博士, 枪   - 我应该不需要那个
Should have taken it.
你应该带着
- Aagh!
- Poor Mr Callum. How are you feeling?
- 啊！  - 可怜的 Callum. 你觉得怎么样？
I can't move my arm.
我动不了我的胳膊了
Move quietly.
慢慢移动
They're all dormant, see?
他们都休眠了, 看？
Evil!
邪恶
No! Quietly. They're only asleep.
不！安静点, 他们只是睡着了
They're not frozen yet.
You watch them. I have things to do.
还没有被冻住．你看着他们, 我还有事要做
Now, let me see.
现在, 让我看看
Yes.
是了
The cryostat! You're freezing them!
低温保持器！你要冻死他们啊!
Klieg!
Klieg!﻿
No! You'll wake them up!
不！你会唤醒他们的！
That is exactly my intention.
那正是我的目的
You still don't understand, do you?
你还是没明白, 是吗？
Their Controller is dead.
他们的管理员已经死了
Now I shall control them.
They will do what I say.
现在我来控制他们, 我说什么他们就做什么
You see, Doctor.
你看, 博士
Yours is the privilege to witness...
你获得了特权, 来见证...
...for the first time the union between
mass power and my absolute intelligence.
...超级力量和我绝对智慧的第一次融合
Who is that?
谁?
Come out.
出来
Come out or I shall kill this man!
出来, 否则我就杀了这个人！
Oh, it's you.
噢, 是你
Go to that wall, all of you.
到墙那里去, 你们全部
All of you!
你们全部过去！
No.
不
I have a better idea, a much better idea.
我有一个好主意, 一个非常好的主意
I shall leave you to the Cybermen.
我要把你们留给赛博人
I'm sure they'll have some use for you.
我肯定他们拿你们有用
Or parts of you!
或者拿你的部件来用！
(KLIEG SCREAMS)
Quick, Jamie! These two levers together.
快, Jamie! 这两根杆一起拉
- I can't shift this one.
- What? You've got to trip that first.
- 我拉不动这个  - 什么？你必须得先按那个
Last time they were frozen
for five centuries.
上一次他们冰冻了五个世纪
This time it must be forever.
这一次必须得是永远
Oh, Doctor!
噢, 博士！
Here we are, Victoria, safe and sound.
Close the hatch.
我们上来了, Victoria, 安然无恙．关上舱门
There we are.
差不多了
Now then.
还有
The best thing about a machine
that makes sense -
一个机器最好的地方是...
you can very easily
make it turn out nonsense.
你可以很容易地把它变成废物
- Now I think you'd better all go outside.
- What are you going to do, Doctor?
- 现在我觉得你们最好都出去  - 你打算干什么，博士？
I'm going to re-electrify the main doors.
我要让主门重新上电
Only this time I'm going to include
the hatch and the control panel.
只不过这次要包含舱门和控制面板
Anyone touching any of them
will get a considerable shock.
任何人碰里面的一个, 都会被电到休克
A fatal one. Now, everyone outside.
很致命的．现在, 所有人都出去
Please take him with you.
I shall be glad to see him outside.
请把他带上跟你一起．我乐意见到他在外面
There we are. That's done.
好了, 完成了
We just have to close the main doors
and the circuit is complete.
我们只要关上主门, 电路就接通了
Thank goodness for that.
感谢上帝
Doctor.
博士
Doctor!
博士！
Jamie...
Jamie...﻿
You go that way. I'll go this way.
你去那边, 我走这边
That gives us more of a chance.
这样胜算大些
When I say run, run.
我喊跑的时候, 跑
Run!
跑！
Quickly!
快点！
Stop! We'll get a shock.
停下！我们会被电的
We must find something to insulate.
That shoring timber.
我们必须找到绝缘的东西. 那些撑柱
Hurry up!
快点！
Hurry up, he's coming!
快啊, 他要过来了！
We must keep him inside
我们必须把他关在里面
or all our work will be wasted.
要不然就前功尽弃了
- I can't hold mine!  - You must!
- 我顶不住了  - 必须顶住
Toberman!
Toberman!﻿
We must survive.
我们必须得活下去
You are evil.
你们是邪恶的
- Toberman, come away!
- You'll get killed, man!
- Toberman, 回来!  - 你会死的, 伙计！
They shall never pass Toberman.
他们永远别想过 Toberman 这关
The door is closed.
门关上了